Elihu Thomson Papers 1865-1944 Mss.Ms.Coll.74
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Professional Correspondence, Ca. 1870-1937; 52 boxes; 26 linear feet
  - Mendel, G. & Company, 1894; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Mendenhall, C. E., 1925; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Mendenhall, Thomas Corwin, 1893-1923; 13 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Mendes, John T., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Merchants National Bank, 1922; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Meriden Britannia Company, 1892; 2 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Merriam, G & C. Company, 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Merrill, Edwin R., 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Merrill & Rogers, Esq., 1913; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Merrimac Chemical Company, 1923-1924; 4 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Merritt, Ernest, 1903-1932; 15 items (Box Series I-35)
    Cornell Univ. & Am. Physical Society
  - Mershon, Ralph D., 1908-1912; 7 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Messageries Anglo-Suisses, 1899; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Meston, C. R., 1906; 3 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Metals and Alloys, 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Metcalf, Joel H., 1913; 4 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Meteor Crater Exploration & Mining Company, 1930-1933; 3 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Meter And Instrument Association, 1905-1907; 2 items (Box Series I-35)
    F. Ortengren
  - Metropolitan Electric League of Boston, 1926; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Metropolitan Magazine, 1895-1896; 2 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Metropolitan Trust Company, 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Mexico, Consul For, 1927; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Meyer, Alfred, 1915-1923; 2 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Meyer, Anne Nathan, 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Meyer, H., 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Michelson, A. A., 1918; 3 items (Box Series I-35)
    Univ. of Chicago45
  - Michigan Mining School, 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Mick, W. H., 1913; 2 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Middleton, & Company, 1894; 2 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Miles Pneumatic Tube Company, 1894-1897; 2 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Miller, Dayton C., 1909-1928; 5 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Miller, John A., 1913; 2 items (Box Series I-35)
    Swarthmore College
  - Miller, W. E., 1906; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Millet, J. B. Company, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Mills & Blanchard, Bankers, 1899; 2 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Mills, F. H. & Company, 1903-1916; 8 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Mills, John H., 1905; 2 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Millward, A. Sydney, 1927; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Minnesota Saving Fund and Investment Company, 1895; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Minor, Charles L., 1930; 2 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Minot, Charles S., 1911; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Minthorn, D., 1893; 4 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Misko, Joseph, 1908; 2 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Mitchell, Fletcher & Company, 1909; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Modern Light and Heat, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Modern Machinery, 1897-1899; 4 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Moehring & Rose, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Mohawk National Bank, 1901; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - [Mohr, D. D.], 1895; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Moizan, William Amedee, 1895; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Moller, H. R., 1895; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Monell, S. H., 1901; 4 items (Box Series I-35)
    N.Y. School of Special Electro-Therapeutics
  - Montreal-James Mines Limited, 1909 (Box Series I-35)
  - Moody, Ambert G., 1912-1914; 14 items (Box Series I-35)
    Northfield Schools
  - Moody, Walter S., 1904-1933; 6 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Moody, William R., 1915; 2 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Mooney, Harry E., 1898; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Moore, Alfred F., 1902-1903; 3 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Moore, A. H., 1913-1924; 3 items (Box Series I-35)
  - Moore, H., 1922; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Moore, Irving B., 1 item (Box Series I-35)
    Globe Rubber Works business card
  - Moore, John J., 1906; 1 item (Box Series I-35)
  - Mordey, William M., 1895-1917; 4 items (Box Series I-36)
    Royal Society
  - Morgan, Charles Langbridge, 1924-1936; 12 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Morgan, Howard W., 1916; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Morgan, J. Pierpont, 1902-1917; 2 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Morgan, W. H., 1920; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
    Morgan Engineering Co.
  - Morgan & Wright, 1906; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Morganthau, J. C. & Company, 1902; 2 items (Box Series I-36)
  - [Morris] to Hart, 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Morris, H. G., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Morris, James, 1897; 2 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Morris, John F. L., 1912; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Morrison, George F., 1923; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Morrison, James F., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Morrow, John T., 1910; 2 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Morse Chain Company. Poole Clock Division, 1929; 3 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Morse, Charles H., 1907; 2 items (Box Series I-36)
    Comm. Of Massachusetts. Committee on Industrial Education
  - Morse, Edward S., 1898-1927; 7 items (Box Series I-36)
    Peabody Museum
  - Morse, Mrs. Edward S., n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Morse, H. W., 1903; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Morse, Samuel F. B., 1891-1892; 3 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Morss, Everett, 1926-1928; 2 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Morten & Company, 1908; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Morton, Henry, 1895-1902; 3 items (Box Series I-36)
    Stevens Institute of Technology
  - Moss, Sanford A., 1914-1932; 3 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Motor Car Journal, 1905; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Mott, S. D., 1902; 3 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Mottelay, Paul F., 1902-1917; 34 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Moultrop, I. E., 1920; 2 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Mount, Richard, 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Mowrey, Charles W., 1898; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Mowry, C. A., 1924-1925; 2 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Moyer, J. A., 1915; 2 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Mudell, George V., 1910; 2 items (Box Series I-36)
    Columbia Univ. Dept. of Physics
  - Mudge, Richard, 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Mueller, Horst, 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - [Mullen], C. E., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Mullen, E. D., 1903; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Mullin, E. H., 1900-1904; 26 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Mundy, Arthur J., 1901-1902; 5 items (Box Series I-36)
    Gray Telephone Co.
  - "Municipality and County", 1895; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Munn & Company, 1899; 2 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Munro, Cyril A., 1932; 2 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Munroe, James P., 1899-1928; 6 items (Box Series I-36)
    Munroe Felt and Paper Co.
  - Munsey, Frank A. Company, 1912; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Musterberg, Hugo, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Murray Hill Hotel, 1898; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Murray, Thomas E., 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Museum of Fine Arts. Boston, 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Museum of Science and Industry, 1929-1931; 6 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Museums of the Peaceful Arts, n.d.; 3 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Mutual Life Insurance Company of New York, 1892-1899; 2 items (Box Series I-36)
  - Mynek, E. M., 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Myrick & Company, n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-36)
  - Nalder Brothers & Thompson, LTD, 1901-1922; 2 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1907-1933; 27 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Allied Relief Committee, 1919; 1 item (Box Series I-37)
  - National Americana Society, 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-37)
  - National Board of Fire Underwriters, 1901; 1 item (Box Series I-37)
  - National Business League of America, 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-37)
  - National Carbon Company, Inc., 1900-1918; 2 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Civic Federation, 1918; 1 item (Box Series I-37)
  - National Committee on Calendar Simplification, 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-37)
  - National Conservation Association, 1919 (Box Series I-37)
  - National Cylopedia of American Biography, 1916-1927; 7 items (Box Series I-37)
    See Also: James T. White & Co.
  - National Economic League, 1927-1932; 2 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Electrical Associations, 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-37)
  - National Electric Light Association, 1890-1895; 22 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Electric Light Association, 1896-1899; 28 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Electric Light Association, 1900-1908; 32 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Electric Light Association, 1909-1918; 35 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Electric Light Association, 1920-1933; 17 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Electric Signaling Company, 1912; 2 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Express Company, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-37)
  - National Fire Protection Association, 1906-1932; 7 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Geographic Society, 1899-1928; 3 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Industrial Conference Board, 1918-1931; 6 items (Box Series I-37)
    See also: M. W. Alexander
  - National Institute of Inventors, 1918-1919; 4 items (Box Series I-37)
    Thomas Howard
  - National Institute of Social Studies, 1932-1936; 2 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Memorial of the United States, 1907; 2 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Museum of Engineering, 1924-1925; 3 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Museum of Engineering and Industry, 1925-1927; 4 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Press Bureau, 1917; 1 item (Box Series I-37)
  - National Press Intelligence Company, 1894; 1 item (Box Series I-37)
  - National Public Service Association, 1911; 1 item (Box Series I-37)
  - National Public Works Department Association, 1920; 1 item (Box Series I-37)
  - National Research Council, 1916-1933; 22 items (Box Series I-37)
    See also National Academy of Sciences
  - National Society for the Promotion of Industrial Education, 1908-1911; 4 items (Box Series I-37)
    Arthur L. Williston
  - National Society of Electro-Therapeutists, 1895-1899; 5 items (Box Series I-37)
  - National Stockman & Farmer, 1905; 1 item (Box Series I-37)
  - National Street Lighting Association, 1896; 1 item (Box Series I-37)
  - National War Work Council, 1918; 1 item (Box Series I-37)
    Y.M.C.A. of the U. S.
  - Nation's Business, 1929-1931; 2 items (Box Series I-37)
  - Nature, 1927-1928; 3 items (Box Series I-37)
  - Nature Magazine, n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-37)
  - Navy League of the United States, 1913-1916; 3 items (Box Series I-37)
    Robert M. Thompson
  - Nelson, N., 1891-1893; 4 items (Box Series I-38)
  - [Neucre, J, Mrs.], 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - New Britain Hardware Manufacturing Company, 1898-1899; 4 items (Box Series I-38)
  - New Boston Arena, 1920; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - Newcomb, Edward C., 1899; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - Newcomb, Simon, 1903; 2 items (Box Series I-38)
  - Newell, F. H., 1921; 2 items (Box Series I-38)
  - New England Association of Chemistry Teachers, 1925; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - New England Council, 1932; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - New England Electric Club, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - New England Hardware Dealers' Association, 1911; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - New England Magazine, 1892-1893; 5 items (Box Series I-38)
  - New England Newspaper Writers' Association, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - New England Paper Box Manufacturers' Association, 1893; 2 items (Box Series I-38)
  - New England Phonograph Company, 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - New England Roentgen-Ray Company, 1926-1933; 8 items (Box Series I-38)
  - New England Telephone and Telegraph Company, 1903; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - Newhall, Howatt, 1903; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - New Hampshire College. Department of Electrical Engineering, 1917; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
    C. E. Hewitt
  - Newman, Robert, 1896; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - Newsom, J. F., 1917-1925; 5 items (Box Series I-38)
  - Newspaper Artists' Association, 1903; 3 items (Box Series I-38)
  - New York Central Station. Parlor Car Office, 1900; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - New York City. Manhattan. Department of Public Works, 1917; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - New York Commercial, 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - New York Edison Company, 1924-1930; 2 items (Box Series I-38)
  - New York Electrical Society, 1891-1922; 19 items (Box Series I-38)
  - New York Herald, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - New York Museum of Science and Industry, 1931; 9 items (Box Series I-38)
  - New York & New Jersey Telephone Company, 1904-1905; 2 items (Box Series I-38)
    E. W. Dennison
  - New York Patent Law Association, 1931; 3 items (Box Series I-38)
  - New York Sun, 1914; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - New York Times, 1913-1933; 6 items (Box Series I-38)
  - New York Tribune, 1893-1894; 4 items (Box Series I-38)
  - New York University. Hall of Fame, 1924-1931; 3 items (Box Series I-38)
  - New York World, 1894-1927; 5 items (Box Series I-38)
  - Niagara Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - Nichols, Edward L., 1908; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
    Cornell University. Dept. of Physics
  - Nichols, Ernest Fox, 1901-1921; 14 items (Box Series I-38)
  - Nichols, L. S., 1910; 2 items (Box Series I-38)
  - Nipher, Francis E., 1900-1903; 3 items (Box Series I-38)
  - Nobel Prize Committee for Physics, 1916; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - Noble, Alfred, 1912; 2 items (Box Series I-38)
  - Norris, James F., 1925; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - North American Review, 1892-1923; 4 items (Box Series I-38)
  - North British & Mercantile Insurance Company, 1903; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - North East Foundrymen's Association, 1903; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - Northeastern University, 1925; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - Northern Clay Company, 1913; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
    P. S. MacMichael
  - Northfield Schools, 1906-1918; 2 items (Box Series I-38)
  - North Shore Athletic Club, 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
    Board of Directors
  - Northwestern Electrical Association, 1898-1912; 3 items (Box Series I-38)
  - Norton, Charles L., 1908-1928; 4 items (Box Series I-38)
  - Norton Company, 1916-1921; 2 items (Box Series I-38)
  - Norton, Edwin, 1899; 2 items (Box Series I-38)
  - Norton, E. J., 1908; 2 items (Box Series I-38)
  - Norton, William, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - Norton, W. J., 1908; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - Noyes, Arthur A., 1908-1916; 10 items (Box Series I-38)
  - Noyes, S. Irving, 1918; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - Nutting, C. C., 1916; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
    State Univ. of Iowa. Dept. of Zoology
  - Nye, A. W., 1906; 2 items (Box Series I-38)
    Curtis Steam Turbine Assoc.
  - Nye, H. A., 1926; 1 item (Box Series I-38)
  - O'Brien, Austin Francis (Mrs.), 1923 (Box Series I-39)
  - Ogburn, William F., 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - O'Hara, John B., 1899; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Ohio State University, 1922-1925; 19 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Oil Paint and Drug Reporter, 1927; 2 items (Box Series I-39)
    H. J. Schnell
  - Old Colony Trust Company, 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Old Corner Book Store, Inc., 1920; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Old Timers and CoWorkers, 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Olken, H., 1933; 5 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Onken, William H., 1926; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Optical Society of America, 1921-1928; 4 items (Box Series I-39)
  - O'Reilly, M. F., 1903; 2 items (Box Series I-39)
    Manhattan College
  - Organ Power Company, 1903-1904; 12 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Orr, Blanche, 1914; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Osaka Electric Lamp Company, 1915; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Osgood, Farley, n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - O-TE-SA-GA, 1913; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Ottengren, F., 1906; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Outlook Company, 1923; 5 items (Box Series I-39)
    Ernest H. Abbott
  - Overall, G. W., 1900; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Owens, James W., 1928-1933; 4 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Owens, R. B., 1898-1912; 4 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Owens, Rodney, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Oxford Club. Lynn, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Pach Brothers, 1913; 4 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Pacific Trucking & Manufacturing Company, 1906; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Packard, C. S. W., 1925; 2 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Packard Motor Company, 1908-1922; 4 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Packer, M. M., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Paget, Leonard, 1893; 2 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Paine, Sidney B., 1901-1930; 6 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Palmros, Alexander, 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Palmyra Chamber of Commerce, 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Panama Canal Commission, 1904; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Pan-American Exposition 1901, 1900-1901; 11 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Pancoast, Charles R., 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Paramet Chemical Corporation, 1922; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Parisian Inventors Academy, 1900; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Parker, A. P., 1922; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Parker, Bowdoin S., 1895; 2 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Parker, Frank J., 1899; 2 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Parkhurst, Walter S. (Mrs.), 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Parry, J. Stanford, 1914; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Parshall, H. F., 1896-1924; 26 items (Box Series I-39)
    See also- Inst. of Civil Engineers & International Elec. Congress
  - Parsons, Benjamin F., 1913; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Parsons, Charles, 1907; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Parsons, Charles A., 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Patten, Mary L., 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Patterson, C. E., 1923; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Pattison, Robert E., 1887; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Patty, Laura E., 1895; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Paul, Alfred, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - [Paul, S. ], n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Pauley, William, 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Payne, W. B., 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Peabody Academy of Science, 1891-1915; 19 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Pebody, G. A., 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Peabody, Houghteling & Company, 1900; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Peabody Museum, 1906-1930; 11 items (Box Series I-39)
    "Old Salem Commercial-Marine Exhibit" Misc. Correspondence
  - Pearl, Raymond, 1929; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
    Johns Hopkins University
  - Pearson,. F. S., 1891-1897; 2 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Pearson, Thomas C., 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Peck, E. F., 1896-1912; 8 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Peck, William E., 1891-1914; 6 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Peckett's on Sugar Hill, 1934; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Peirce, Emily Osgood, 1929; 3 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Peirce, H. B., 1935; 3 items (Box Series I-39)
    Verein Deutscher Ingenieure Medal of Honor
  - Pember, John E., [1923?]; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Pender, Harold, 1913-1924; 8 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Penn Club, 1929; 2 items (Box Series I-39)
    E. Clinton Rhoads
  - Pennie, Davis, Marvin and Edmonds, 1921; 4 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Penn Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1897; 3 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Pennock, Edward, 1898-1933; 7 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Pennock, J. D., 1919; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
    Solvay Process Co.
  - Penn State Engineer, 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
  - Pennsylvania. Coolidge and Dawes, 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
    4th of July Club
  - Pennsylvania Department of Public Instruction, 1917; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
    Bureau of Vocational Ed.
  - Pennsylvania Glass Sand Company, 1 item (Box Series I-39)
    S. S. Woods to D. M. Barringer
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1891-1904; 4 items (Box Series I-39)
  - Pennsylvania Salt Manufacturing Company, 1930; 1 item (Box Series I-39)
    Leonard Beale
  - Percy, Lund, Humphries & Company, LTD., 1924-1925; 3 items (Box Series I-40)
    Transactions of the First World Power Conf.
  - Perin, C. P., 1925; 2 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Perkins, Charles A., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
    Univ. of Tennessee. Dept. of Electrical Engineering
  - Perpetual Encyclopedia Corporation, 1925-1929; 3 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Perrin, John G., 1899; 2 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Perrine, Frederic A. C., 1897-1904; 8 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Perry, Frank L., 1898-1906; 4 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Perry, J. F., 1892; 2 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Perry, John, 1902; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Perry, William P., 1900; 2 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Peters, George H., 1900; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
    Naval Observatory
  - Pevear, H. A., 1891-1902; 4 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Phalder, F., 1891; 2 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Phelan, Adeline R., n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Phelan, James J., 1931-1932; 2 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Phelps, George M., 1889; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Phelps, Myron H., 1905; 2 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Phenix, G. P., 1896; 3 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Philadelphia Commercial Museum, 1923; 6 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Philadelphia Electrical Exposition, 1898; 2 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Phillips, B. F., 1899; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Phillips, Charles F., 1895; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Phillips, F. A., 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Phipps, Howard J., and Company, 1903; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Phoenix Dynamo Manufacturing Company, 1911; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
    Robert Pohl
  - Physical Review, 1898-1903; 3 items (Box Series I-40)
    E. L. Nichols
  - Pickard, Greenleaf Whittier, 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Pickering, Earl C., 1903-1920; 32 items (Box Series I-40)
    Harvard College Observatory
  - Pickering, William H., 1924; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Pierce, John M., 1907; 2 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Pierce, Stuart, 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
    Ocean Boulevard Bridge Co.
  - Pierson, W. A., 1900; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Pi Gamma Mu, 1928; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
    National Social Science Honor Society
  - Pihl, Victor E., 1891; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Pinkham, Max, 1934; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
    Note to Mrs. Thomson
  - Pittsburgh Electric Club, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company, 1917; 12 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Pittsburgh Testing Laboratory, 1932; 3 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Plantacion Rubio, 1903; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
    Tehuantepec Rubber Culture Co.
  - Planters Compress Company, 1900; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Pogolski, N. T., 1899-1903; 5 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Polytechnic High School, 1913; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
    A. L. Jordan
  - Poor's Publishing Company, 1923; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
    C. C. Houghton
  - Pope, Franklin Leonard, 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Pope Manufacturing Company, 1905; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Pope, Ralph W., 1897-1910; 23 items (Box Series I-40)
    See A. I. E. E.
  - Popular Astronomy, 1928; 2 items (Box Series I-40)
    C. H. Gingrich
  - Popular Electricity Publishing Company, 1908-1910; 6 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Popular Mechanics Magazine, 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Popular Radio, 1922; 12 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Popular Science Institute, 1929-1930; 5 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Porter, E. L., 1931; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Porter, Thomas F., 1903; 2 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Portugese Consul, 1897; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Post, [Augusta], 1910; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Potter, William B., 1918-1933; 3 items (Box Series I-40)
  - POWER, 1921; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Power, D. B. H. & Company, n.d.; 1 item (Box Series I-40)
  - Power Wagon, 1913; 2 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Powers, Samuel J., 1904; 2 items (Box Series I-40)
  - Pratt, Francis C., 1923-1925; 3 items (Box Series I-41)
  - Pratt, James W., 1933; 1 item (Box Series I-41)
  - Pratt, Joseph H., 1927-1928; 3 items (Box Series I-41)
  - Pratt, W. H., 1909; 1 item (Box Series I-41)
  - Preece, William H., 1885-1907; 4 items (Box Series I-41)
  - Prescott, George B., 1892; 1 item (Box Series I-41)
  - President of the United States, 1897-1899; 2 items (Box Series I-41)